crystalvaults.com 2018-09-24

# Privacy Policy | Crystal Vaults

#### We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it to process your order. 

#### We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to process your order and deliver it to you. 

####   
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. We keep only the addresses, phone numbers, and emails that you put in your profile. You can see all information, and delete it as you wish. 

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact us at info@CrystalVaults.com. 

It is Crystal Vaults policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

##   
Website Visitors

Like most website operators, we collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our website.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information 

Certain visitors to Crystal Vaults choose to interact with in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a newsletter at to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with us by purchasing items fare asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, we collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with us. Crystal Vaults does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Crystal Vaults discloses potentially personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, need to know that information in order to process and ship orders. All have agreed not to disclose it to others. We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Crystal Vaults will disclose potentially personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request,. If you are a registered user of the Crystal Vaults website and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Crystal Vaults and our products. We primarily use our newsletter to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. Crystal Vaults takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying information.

##   
Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Crystal Vaults uses cookies to help us identify visitors, their usage of of the website, and their website access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Crystal Vaults website, with the drawback that certain features of such as saved shopping carts may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

##   
Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Crystal Vaults may change its Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy P. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
